Wavenumber	Wavenumber listed, can be listed +/- 5 cm-1 different than in the associated literature due to differences in device settings/gratings. Color indicates relative peak intensity: weak/medium/strong
biomolecule	Type of biomolecule listing is associated with. F.e. Proteins (include amino acids, extracellular matrix-related components, carrier proteins)
specifications	specific biomolecule associated with this wavenumber
component/group	specific chemical bond/group associated with this wavenumber
specifics on vibration	type of vibration contributing to this wavenumber
Lit#	References
